[Music]
So, like this, we need to wrap the whole neem leaves in a bracelet, and
this is called Bona Muthu for our Bonas. We
can find this in the Pooja store, and we can also make it at home
. [Music] We need to take a photo of the eggs.  [Laughter]
What is anarchy?
This is the special sambar spice in our soup [clears throat].
Hi Namaste Welcome to Naveen Ultimate
Channel So today we have Bonalu at our house. Every
year we watch our Bonalu vlog
and this year too, like similar vlogs,
where are we going to prepare Bonalu and how are we preparing it?
So many people do not know.
Andhra people also watch it. So if
you are interested in what is Bonalu and how is it prepared, then
watch it. It would be very good to make Bonalu and
offer it to the goddess.
Bonalu means the offering made at our house. Actually, we have to
make it in a clay pot and take that clay pot and
go and give it to the goddess.
But we have become a little bit fancy,
so we are also showing off as fancy.
Many people ask why we
have let our hair down. No matter who you
see, no matter who you
see, the mother will have full
loose hair like this, with full red dots and
red sarees. So it is not
wrong for us to let our hair down like this, it is not
wrong for the mother, but many
people will not accept this, so I
am giving a disclaimer in advance.  And here are
my puja items, what offerings we are
cooking and what prasad we are giving to the goddess. All
these are bona fides, meaning
we are the only ones who do it. We
call our neighbors to come over and serve food. I
do it every year as well. This year too,
my friends are
coming, so I prepare all the items for them.
And here is the
kitchen. Today, the kitchen is not as beautiful
because it is busy cooking, so
my mommy cooks the prasad.  Today, they will
offer alms as a gift to the mother. They will offer alms,
so the
alms is already here and they will
put green vegetables here, so mommy will have green vegetables.
This is the green gift.
This is the green gift. Green
vegetables, green vegetables, green soup.
I put them there.
So now we are making bonam.
We have put turmeric, sandalwood and
saffron in it.  They are usually
placed in clay pots, but since I found designer pots, I
thought it was great that they came with a full work of art with the face of the mother.  This little pot
also got a set [music] like this.  These are
reusable and
can be used happily every year, but I don't think I'll use them. I'll just
buy new ones every year.  Normally, the dot is
decorated with yellow saffron.
Last year, in my last year's
videos, I put it in clay pots
with decorations. But since it is already decorated,
we don't need it much, just
adding yellow saffron is
enough.
So, they also add green curry paste, green vegetables and
green yogurt.
[Music]
I'm putting the next green in the middle like this. [Music] I'm going to put a piece of string here and
add the paramam.
[Music]
So, the mother really likes to wrap the whole neem tree like this, so she
puts a small pot on top like this.  And in this, we
should tie a green chili bracelet to our bones. [Music]
[Music]
This is called the earth's strength.  We
can find this in the Pooja store and we
can also make [music] at home.
This paste should be soaked for a while.
[Music]
These are 3 kg per quarter, 11 servings, okay, that's what I'm going to do in the
future. Remember
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] For
my mother [Music] Name
[Music]
Two vakkas, as well as bangles, are
offered to my mother. Onions are offered.
Today, I don't know why. They put jaggery,
put dal,
and coconut.
So this is another final plating.
Today, it is compulsory for our feet. Whoever is
carrying the bonam should have turmeric on their feet.
Now [Music] The bonam should first be
placed near our house god. [
Music] [
Music] [Music] [Music] [
Bell]
Oh
[Music] They should burn
incense all over the house.
So, to get rid of all the negativity in the house, they are at my mother's house.
[Music]
[Music] [
Music] [
Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music] [
Music] [Music
]
[Music]
Hey
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music]
Hallelujah
[Music] [Music]
Rupees
[Music]
[Music] [
Music]
[Music]
[Music] [Music] [Music] [Music] [
Music] The
puja went very well and
now my mom and I are doing a cooking program for the guests who come to our house in the evening
.  My mom's
specialized sambar. Actually, sambar is
eaten in many places.
But my mom has a separate genre. I will
also show you the recipe for making sambar. I will
show you what I cook. I use
AS brand palli oil. It tastes good to
us. And how many
red chillies are in it? Mustard is also good.
I am making chicken before it gets too soft.
[Music] This is 4 kgs of chicken. I
washed it. It is already ready. Actually,
we have a habit of washing it four times.
Many people say that you should
not wash the chicken. But I do not understand how you eat it with its smell. I make sure that I wash it at least four times with
vinegar. That is also
onions, green chillies
in sambar. But vegetables are good, so
fenugreek,
okra, etc.
[Music]
Now I'm marinating the chicken until the tomatoes, carrots, and all those vegetables are tender
.
Next, I'll
add a little more of the alli mellipayala paste. My mommy
made it. If it's not enough,
let's see.
It's a bit runny and the eyes don't want it to
melt.
[Music] It's like
yogurt to make it a little softer.
[Music]
So I'll leave it to marinate for half an hour or an hour. The
taste is
good.  And now the next
process is to add
a little turmeric to the sambar. After all these vegetables are cooked,
turmeric is okay. Actually, I don't
know how to add sambar. I'm learning my mom's
recipe of sambar today
.  I will save this video
.
This is sambar curry. This is homemade
sambar curry.
This is what my mommy made. You brought it from your village.
This is the special sambar curry in my chira. This is what I like about
this sambar curry.
Two spoons.
Now add some water to it. Let the
pieces cook. Hello.
What am I doing?
I am boiling eggs. I have a tray of
eggs. I am
making my favorite recipe with eggs.
[Music]
So, let's cook it for 15 or 20
minutes. And let's add tamarind rice. Let's add a
little bit. Now finally,
this is the lentil. This is
called kandipappu. This is for me.
Let's see when I make it in the future.
Okay. What is sambar?
What else should I add to it? Add asafoetida.
Add sambar powder. Add jaggery. A
little bit. Are all of them there? Okay. Okay.
One.  I need to add coriander
and now I'm going to add jaggery next.
My mommy said that
jaggery is a special touch in sambar. Some
people don't need it. It tastes good.
Some people don't like it. Some people like it light and spicy. Some
people don't like it. They add actual jaggery.
So the whole thing is sambar.
Now I'll show you how we're doing chicken curry and bagara rice at the
same time, in our style
[of music].
What is this?
This is Shajira.
Okay,
put Shajira in the chicken. Okay,
put Shajira in the chicken.  Even if you add a little garam masala, if you add a
few cloves like this, it's okay, okay,
a little cardamom will smell good.
Onions and tomatoes should be fried in chicken and onions in chicken.
And now we are already frying the oil in the bagara. Let's add
cardamom, cardamom, cardamom, okay, let's add all
this.
Even if we add more, it
won't be good again.
I don't know what this is called. If you know, comment
in the comment section.
Nutmeg, mace
[Music] Now we add a little tomato to the chicken. Because we
want it to be a little like gravy, the
tomato and ginger are mixed
in [Music] So we should add it in
this.
Okay, onion, green chilli, bagara,
rice, onions and green chilli, carrots,
beans, carrots,
beans, and potatoes.
Children will eat it with pleasure.
Okay, my mommy,
how much water is needed for 2/2 kg of rice?
How many cans of biryani did you put in?
Next, you should put chicken in it.
[Music]
[Music] Let's
work with a hammer. Take a photo of the same eggs.
Witch I [Music] Hate, actually, actually,
this is Bobby, let's tell him too. Bobby,
take a photo of the eggs.  [Laughter]
What do you mean, Arachakam, I
took a photo of all the eggs and said, "
Chicken curry is ready." Here it is. While
bringing it down, I added kasturi methi and garam masala
and I will also add Everest chicken masala. And this is the
tint.
Here is the bagara rice. These are the two things done.
Now let's get the next two items
ready.
[Music]
This is something that bachelors like the most. In
our house, we make it
more if we are bachelors. It would be
easier because there is no one who likes to cook that much. We make sure that it is
easy in our house. Unfortunately,
my mom is the only one who
cooks for us.  And we put it for cutting, so it's a
day, and this is very tasty, actually, we
say bachelor, but bachelor curries are
very good, but this is just like a
roast.
[Music]
And I have also boiled oil on this side, I
will add sprouts in it, all these are mixed
sprouts, healthy food,
protein and fiber. Actually,
if you fry the whole eggs in oil like this, the taste is very, very
good, especially if you don't
like egg yolks, fry them a little in oil,
add salt and pepper and eat.  So, as soon as the
cooking was done, all our friends
came to our house for a meal. But the
specialty here is that I am
celebrating something else. On this day, it is the same
Masraya's send-off party. It is said that Masrayas got a
seat in engineering and is
going to another hostel. So, he will be at
home for the last two or three days,
so now we are all going to have a send-
off party together.
All the details of this vlog will
be coming next. I will release it tomorrow.
Definitely watch it. Thank you, boy.